ANDREA PERERA



I 5 A PO@QUEENSU.CA ANDREAX PERERA@GMAIL.COM



(416) 893-7813



LINKEDIN.COM/IN/ANDREAPO

PORTFOLIO WEBSITE ANDREAPERERA.ME

OBJECTIVE

I am a third year student and entrepreneur at Queen's University studying Software Design hoping to build new experiences and grow as a programmer and designer. I strive to be a part of something innovative and creative, as well as work in a positive environment with others.

SKILLS

- Excellent Computer skills
- Quick learner

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMPUTING (HONOURS) IN SOFTWARE DESIGN (2016-2020)

Queen's University

Dean's Honour List 2018, Code The Change 2018 Winner, Member of Software Developer's Club, Participant in MLH's Local Hack Day, Attended CUSEC 2017 and 2019, QHacks 2017 Volunteer, Computing Orientation Leader 2017, QHacks 2018 and 2019 Participant

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

St. Joseph Secondary School

Achieved honour roll status all four years and two subject achievement awards. Member of Junior and Senior Volleyball Team, Varsity Softball Team, Latin Club, and Prom Committee. Took several AP courses.

EXPERIENCE

CO-FOUNDER, CMO INFIELD ID INC.

June 2018 - Present

InField ID is an AI AgriTech startup helping researchers quickly identify plant pests and invasive species to save time, money and effort. Awarded third place and \$10k at the Dunin-Deshpande Pitch Competition. Responsible for web development, online presence, graphic design, company branding and outreach.

IT MANAGER, EXECUTIVE TEAM QUEEN'S SOFTWARE DEVELOPER'S CLUB

September 2018 - Present — Queen's University
Helping to manage and upkeep the current website of the Queen's
Software Developing Club on WordPress as well as creating and
designing an entirely new one.

WEBSITE CONTENT ASSISTANT HEART AND STROKE FOUNDATION

May 2017 - September 2017

Supported web content delivery planning and execution with the Content and Project Management Teams. Updated and published

- Proficient in Python, Java, C, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Haskell, Prolog
- Proficient in Adobe XD, Sketch
- Fluent in Spanish (readwrite-speak)
- Studied French for 10 years
- Strong work ethic
- Strong interpersonal skills
- Excellent trouble shooter
- Entrepreneurial skills

website content using HTML and enterprise CMS. Currently a part-time, contract worker, publishing new content when needed.

EXTRACURRICULAR AND VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

CODE THE CHANGE 2018 WINNER

April 2018 – Queen's University

Worked with a team to design a responsive website for UNICEF Queen's in under 12 hours. Used HTML, CSS, Bootstrap. Won 1st place.

QUEEN'S COMPUTING ORIENTATION

February 2017 - September 2017

Helped facilitate Queen's Computing orientation week (student-run) as an orientation leader. Prepared and guided the incoming class of 2021 by participating in activities on and off campus. Received training in areas such as inclusivity, safety, accessibility, intercultural awareness, and mental health.

QHACKS 2017 - VOLUNTEER

February 2017 - Queen's University

Assisted organizing committee with logistics; food distribution, escorting attendees around university campus, etc.

PAMILY BHARDWAJ LAW OFFICE

July 2012 - May 2016

Assisted lawyers and paralegals by helping with administration (phone calls), filing and organizing documents.

REFERENCES

LEE TAYLOR

Senior Manager, Health Information Services
Heart and Stroke Foundation, lee.taylor@heartandstroke.ca

PAMILA BHARDWAJ

Lawyer Bhardwaj Law Office, (416) 488-6292

TATIANA CANETT

Accountant
Tatiana Canett Accounting Services, (905) 330-1085